Guide to the Nine Mile Run Greenway Project Records, 1945-2005 AIS.2006.19A
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Audio-Visual Material, 1996-1999; X.
  - VHS, 1996-c2000; 6.
    - "Riparian Forest Buffers", Undated (Box 14, Item 15)
    - "RMI-Intro, Hunter Tour", Undated (Box 15, Item 1)
    - "RMI Charette no. 1: Introduction, Site Tour", Undated (Box 15, Item 2)
    - "Squirrel Hill Nine Mile Run Development Public Hearing Tape no. 1", March 27, 1997 (Box 15, Item 3)
    - "Squirrel Hill Nine Mile Run Development Public Hearing Tape no. 2", March 27, 1997 (Box 15, Item 4)
    - "Stream Walk Master", Undated (Box 15, Item 5)
    - "Stream Walk: Nine Mile Run", Undated (Box 15, Item 6)
    - "Swisshelm Park Community Meeting Tape no. 1", April 2, 1997 (Box 15, Item 7)
    - "Up the Mon no. 1", May 11, 1999 (Box 15, Item 8)
    - "Up the Mon no. 2", May 11, 1999 (Box 15, Item 9)
    - "Up the Mon no. 3", May 11, 1999 (Box 15, Item 10)
    - "Views of Nine Mile Run: A Landscape Transformed by Industry", Undated (Box 15, Item 11)
    - "Wood Street Nine Mile Run Community Workshop no. 1", Undated (Box 15, Item 12)
    - "Wood Street Nine Mile Run Community Workshop no. 2", Undated (Box 15, Item 13)
    - "Wood Street Nine Mile Run Community Workshop no. 3", Undated (Box 15, Item 14)
- Maps, c1995-2000; XI.
  This series contains maps that were used during the Nine Mile Run Greenway project. The "Ledger Sized" maps consist mainly of maps with their printed reports concerning population, waste water run-off, pedestrian routes, and tributaries related to the Nine Mile Run site. The oversized maps are housed in five separate file-folders. Of note is the neighborhoods map folder that shows the Nine Mile Run Greenway neighborhood borders and the municipality that is responsible for the various sections of the Nine Mile Run Greenway area. The neighborhoods portrayed include, but are not limited to, the City of Pittsburgh, Swissvale, Edgewood, and Wilkinsburg.
  - Ledger-sized Maps, c1995-2000 (Box 16)
  - Oversized Maps -- Aerial (Map-case 32-2, Folder 1)
  - Oversized Maps -- Data Collected (Map-case 32-2, Folder 2)
  - Oversized Maps -- Neigborhoods (Map-case 32-2, Folder 3)
  - Oversized Maps -- Planning (Map-case 32-2, Folder 4-5)